In this exercise, we're setting up a NAT gateway and private subnet.
在此练习中 我们将设置 NAT 网关和专用子网
We can find our NAT gateways in VPC.
我们可以在 VPC中找到我们的 NAT 网关
We look at our NAT gateway that is built.
我们查看已构建的 NAT 网关
The routing table should have the NAT gateway as the target.
路由表应该将 NAT 网关作为目标
So once we create a NAT gateway,
一旦我们创建了 NAT 网关
we will then want to use and include that NAT gateway within a routing table.
然后 我们将使用并包含该 NAT 网关在路由表中
So we can see we have a NAT gateway here in our new VPC.
我们可以看到我们在新的 VPC中有一个 NAT 网关
What we'll want to do is look at our routing tables.
我们要做的是看看我们的路由表
We can see that in our routing table that we set up, we have,
我们可以看到在我们设置的路由表中 我们有
again as we saw in other exercises,
就像我们在其他演习中看到的一样
that we've got a local route,
我们有一条当地路线
and then we've got the default or the 0.0.0/0 route within our route table,
然后我们在航线表中找到了默认的或 0.0.0/0 的路线
this time we're pointing at the NAT gateway that we just took a look at.
这一次我们指向的是我们刚刚看到的 NAT 网关
Once you've got the route table set up,
一旦你有了路线表
then it's a matter of looking at our subnets and
那是看我们的子网
having the subnets also set up to use this route table.
子网也设置为使用此路由表
So we have a subnet here for this exercise.
所以我们在这里有一个子网来进行这项工作
Within the subnet view,
在子网视图中
we can look at the route table again to see that
我们可以再看看路线表看看
we're pointing at the route table we just looked at,
我们指向的是我们刚刚看到的路线表
and now anything within this subnet we'll use obviously this route table.
现在这个子网里的任何东西我们都会使用这个路由表
This route table has a default route going through our NAT gateway
此路由表具有穿过我们的 NAT 网关的缺省路由